<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Aura Candy</title>
    <link href="https://eyecandyaura.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://eyecandyaura.com" />
    <updated>2021-02-17T23:54:53+04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AuraCandy</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://eyecandyaura.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>123</title>
        <author>
            <name>AuraCandy</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://eyecandyaura.com/123/"/>
        <id>https://eyecandyaura.com/123/</id>

        <updated>2021-02-17T23:54:53+04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Hi! I'm Aura Candy&nbsp; 123 Wanna watch me live?&nbsp;&nbsp; See my twitter &gt;&gt;&nbsp; Hi! I'm Aura Candy Wanna watch me live? See my twitter &gt;&gt; Hi! Yeah, I'm Aura Candy I'm a broadcaster on that adult website - Chaturbate. As by now i mainly&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <h1 id="hi-im-aura-candynbspbr">
      Hi! I'm Aura Candy&nbsp;<br>
    </h1>

  <p>
    123
  </p>

  <p>
    Wanna watch me live?&nbsp;&nbsp;<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    See my twitter &gt;&gt;&nbsp;
  </p>

  <p>
    Hi! I'm Aura Candy
<br>Wanna watch me live?
<br>See my twitter &gt;&gt;
<br>
<br>Hi! Yeah, I'm Aura Candy
<br>I'm a broadcaster on that adult website - Chaturbate. As by now i mainly appear on Twitter and Chaturbate. Grab the link to my live broadcast on my Twitter. When i broadcast? Whenever. What i broadcast? Whatever. If you bookmark this page and come back later there might be something new. One day. Thanks for checking my personal page out! If you want to see my twitter, it's @EyeCandyAura
<br>Questions Answered
<br>How do i know you're online?
<br>Follow me on Chaturbate - you'll get notified when i'm online. As for my schedule - i'm still figuring it out.
<br>Where do i watch you for free?
<br>Watching my broadcast is free on Chaturbate. 
<br>How do i get a recording of your broadcast?
<br>Hop in on Chaturbate when i broadcast and request a private show - you get my private show saved automatically in your 'my collection' which you can access by clicking on your username on top right.
<br>How do i know if you do stuff i like in a private show? 
<br>Visit me when i'm online and ask a question in a tip note, in a private message or if you're ok with that in public chat, if it's active.
<br>Are custom requests private show only?
<br>Mostly they are but a lot of requests i do in a public show just ask me when i'm live.
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
